This arrow is irreplaceable.
There's only one, you know.
It's essential to my mission.
Losing it is not an option.
Leave that arrow right there!
He'll bleed out!
Because of my blockhead brother,
I have no choice but to kill you now.
You do know
nothing can happen to this arrow.
I can't let it break or catch the eye
of some neighborhood crone.
I tend to be very meticulous,
you see.
It is in my nature to return
this arrow to its proper place.
Certainly, after listening
to one CD in its entirety
you return it to its case
before listening to another?
That is what
everyone does.
That is what I do.
Oh? So you've decided to
enter our abode?
No shit, Sherlock!
How else would I beat your ass
and bring Koichi back to normal?!
Bro! I'm not down
for the count yet!
Wait for me
before you attack!
Attack?
This fight's just getting started!
Up there, in the dark…
something's coming!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 4
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 2
Okuyasu…
Your stupidity is all-encompassing.
If you hadn't stumbled in here,
Worse Company would have
already destroyed Josuke.
What's more, you
walked right into the line of fire.
Bro…
Your Stand, The Hand,
may be menacing,
but you, little brother,
are a sad sack.
The incompetent will
always hinder the capable…
I've told you over and over,
ever since we were children.
Plus, life is only worth living
when it has growth…
You've heard that
from me many times, too…
What the hell
are these wounds?
What kind of attack leaves
damage like that?
Whatever it is,
he's hiding something.
Little brother.
You know, it's idiots like you
who deserve to die like
a roach on its back!
More tiny holes!
What the hell is doing that?
Shining Diamond!
You're gonna attack
your brother, too?!
Josuke Higashikata…
He'd never abandon
this little brat, Koichi.
He'll be back for sure.
I'll be the one to blot him out…
I'll kill anyone who gets in the way
of this bow and arrow,
anyone with a pulse!
Now, then… I think it's time
you tell me 'bout your brother's Stand.
What is his Stand?
Spill it, and I'll get rid of
these holes on your face.
Like… I'd tell you…
You sucker…
Oh well…
Then I guess,
that's the way it's gonna be!
All right, I'm going in.
Just stay outta my way, Okuyasu.
Koichi's living on
borrowed time!
His Stand's gonna attack
from somewhere in the dark.
This is definitely gonna suck.
Senses, don't fail me now..
Hey, where are you going!
Huh?
Why, Josuke?
Why did you heal me?
Pipe down. Later, later.
I might attack you!
I am your enemy!
You serious?
Depends on your answer!
Why did you heal me?
I'm not some genius.
Hurry up and tell me already!
And what about your hand?!
He got you when you were
pulling me out here, didn't he?
Why the hell'd you go
through all that to save me?
Nothing too complicated.
Didn't think anyone
needed to die.
That's all.
Koichi..
He was taken upstairs.
I'm not done
asking questions, Josuke!
What the hell?!
Now, please,
just let me save Koichi!
Why?!
Why don't you use your Stand
to fix your hand?
Just make it all better
like you did my face!
My Shining Diamond can't
heal my own wounds.
Life isn't always easy, is it?
And there's another thing…
No matter how hard I try,
I can't bring back the dead.
Last thing, Okuyasu.
I don't know how yet,
but if Koichi doesn't make it,
I'm gonna punish your brother.
So be pissed off at him!
This is all your brother's fault.
Got it?
If you do,
stay outside.
Koichi!
Shit… This is all a trap.
He'll ambush me as
soon as I get close to Koichi
But…
Trap or not,
now's all I got!
Koichi hasn't a second to spare!
What?!
Okuyasu, you bastard!
Josuke!
Koichi…
I don't have smarts.
I think with my heart
instead of my head.
Once, and only once, I'll repay you
for what you did for me.
But nothing more.
I won't help my Bro,
and I won't do anything
beyond what I promised you.
This is it.
That's great to hear, Okuyasu.
You held up pretty
great back there, Koichi!
Can't tell you how happy I am
to see you awake.
So how many fingers?
Five…
I remember my neck was slammed
in between the gates,
and then, uh… um…
Wh-Where are we?
Hate to break it to you,
Koichi,
but things haven't
gotten any better.
Nothing I'd like more than
to walk down those stairs
and get
the hell out of here.
But something tells me Okuyasu's bro
wouldn't exactly comply…
There's definitely
something up there.
Something's lurking
where I can't see it.
What was that?
Something scurried that way
Josuke, what's going on?
Koichi, I know none of this
makes any sense,
but for now, keep quiet,
and stay close.
It was a helluva lot creepier
when I couldn't see it.
Getting that peek was a relief
Looks like we've got
a little runt on our hands.
As soon as that little shit
shows himself,
I'll blast him to kingdom come
with Shining Diamond
There you are!
What the…?
There's a ton of them!
And they're in uniform…
Wh-What's…
We're being ambushed
by a bunch of toy paratroopers…
This is his brother's Stand?
Ow!
Mother…!
Getting just two or three
of 'em won't be enough.
They leave small wounds,
but they can definitely do some damage.
They'll hurt us bad
if we try to fight them.
Since Okuyasu decided to
meddle and save that brat,
my plan has gone
somewhat awry.
But you'll never escape
this house…
or the domination of my perfectly
synchronized Stand,
Worse Company!
WORSE COMPANY
KEICHO NIJIMURA
Worse Company?
Josuke, wh-what's…
Questions later.
I know this is crazy…
Keep quiet and stay back!
Shit's about to hit the fan!
All units, halt!
Ready, aim…
Fire!
Left face!
Damn, head on, they've got the
fire power to blow us to smithereens!
Lucky!
We've got windows!
Koichi, I know
it's the second floor,
but we've gotta break
those windows and jump to safety.
So much for that idea…
Great…
They've got helicopters.
They're using U.S. Army
Apache helicopters?!
Look out! A tank!
Those are definitely tanks.
Koichi, be caref–
What?
Wh-What did you just say,
Koichi? You can see them?
The soldiers, tanks,
and helicopters…
All of them?
Yeah. I don't understand what's
going on, but I can see them.
So that arrow…
it did give you a Stand!
Oh? So the shrimp got one!
He's finally got the power
to use a Stand, huh?!
So, if it isn't Okuyasu's bro.
Pretty ballsy move there…
Showing off your Stand like that!
Think of my Stand, Worse Company,
as a cast-iron defense.
It renders any attack or
intruder utterly inert.
I know you're just itching
to put me out of commission…
But I promise you
your Shining Diamond's attacks
will never get
anywhere close to me!
Feast your eyes on this!
The perfect symmetry of my
army's formation is stunning, isn't it?
All units, maintain battle
formation! At ease!
There's nothing like having
everything beautifully in place.
Though you did knock off
a few of my foot soldiers back there,
so my troop's formation is
irritatingly imperfect now.
You are a meticulous bastard,
aren't you?
You came out here
to tell us that?
No, my reason for
showing myself
is to observe you,
little trouble maker.
M-Me?
Indeed.
Koichi, was it?
How ironic that you appear to have
the innate capability for Stands.
Manifest your Stand immediately,
and show me what it can do.
You might just have the power
I've been looking for!
Do it, and I'll let you live!
B-But…
The ability
you're looking for?
Just what the hell
are you trying to do?
I'll be asking the questions
around here, Josuke!
Keep in mind I still have you
in my crosshairs!
Be grateful you got
to live this long!
Great.
Hey, what're you waiting for?
Manifest your Stand, brat!
S-Stand? I don't have a clue
of what you're talking about!
What?
This is your first time?
No wonder!
Very well! Josuke, show him how
to manifest his Stand!
Huh?
Your Shining Diamond's range
is a measly one meter.
If the little wimp's Stand
can compensate for yours,
you might be able to
escape my Company.
True… A Stand that could
kick your ass would be awesome.
Okay, materializing your
Stand is easy, Koichi.
All you've got to do is
ramp up the urge to protect
yourself, or to beat him into a pulp.
Huh?
The rest is instinct.
A Stand unique to your
spiritual energy should reveal itself.
W-Wait!
You can't just
spring that on me
and expect me
to know what to do!
Don't know what to do, huh?
Then I suppose I'll just have to
give you the inspiration!
Do it, Green Beret!
What?!
That's…
Come on, Koichi,
try moving it.
M-Move what?
That Stand!
Stand?
I-I made this thing?!
Okay, now what?
What can this
egg-shaped thing do?
What can it do?
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but that's all I've got!
That's it!
What?
That's it?!
This Stand..
Enough! I've seen all
I need to see!
All units, ready!
Koichi, withdraw your Stand!
If they destroy your Stand,
you'll die, too!
Withdraw?
How do I make it withdraw?!
Attack!
J-Josuke!
Excellent. Koichi and Josuke
have been separated
The crack in that egg…
The brat doesn't realize it,
but he might have something there.
The only man dying here
is Josuke.
Ouch…
Hey, bro,
if you're gonna bring
down this dump in a ball of fire,
then quit playing around
and bring it!
I'm in the mood for
a great brawl.
Josuke Higashikata…
Is it true you
strongly disapprove of
disparaging remarks
about your hair?
Why don't you go ahead
and find out for yourself?
No, that won't be
necessary.
I'll blow off your head right
from underneath
that prized hair of yours;
consider yourself forewarned.
But first, Worse Company will
fire bullets into your legs.
Running away
will be impossible.
Next we'll take aim
at your arms.
You'll have
no means of defense.
That's when I finally
get to blow away
your brains
and your hair.
Interesting. Sounds like
a bullet-proof tactic to me…
That is, if you overlook that
it's completely impossible!
I tend to be very meticulous,
you see.
When I say I'll do something,
I do it.
Thus the forewarning.
He's wide open…
I just need to make
that Stand thing appear again.
It's only an egg,
but if I can somehow hurl it at him,
I might be able to beat him!
I-I can do this!
Time to suck it up!
I'm gonna beat him!
Your Stand intrigues me,
so I'll let you live for now!
You bastard!
All units, charge!
Like Moses parting the
waters of the Red Sea,
I'm gonna break through
your army and beat you down!
Fool!
My plan is proceeding
exactly as I forewarned,
Josuke Higashikata!
A l-landmine?!
First, your legs will go!
And now, Apaches,
fire your missiles!
My arm…
First the legs, then the arms.
It feels so wonderful when
things go exactly as predicted.
I wonder if your wounded arms
will save you as
Worse Company
pummels you
with every one of its missiles,
shells, and rounds!
You lose,
Josuke Higashikata!
All units!
Ready, aim…!
And what do you think you're
doing, Josuke Higashikata?
Finally accepting your fate?
Are you asking me
to let you go?
Well, no can do.
All units, fire!
I've already
implemented my tactics.
What?!
Those are the missiles
I shot at Josuke's arm…
Those are my missiles!
Did ya forget?
My Shining Diamond repairs
stuff that's broken.
If you're getting forgetful,
you might want to
start taking notes.
You know,
meticulously.
EPISODE 5
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 3